https://www.ezone.com/help/privacy.htm

Ezone Privacy Statement
Ezone PTY PTD has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate
our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering
and dissemination practices for our website (Ezone.com) and apps.
This site contains links to other sites. Ezone is not responsible
for the privacy practices or the content of such Websites.
Registering and giving us personal information is not required.
We don't share specific information with third parties. We don't sell addresses
to third parties.
Third Party Advertising
We use the following third-party advertising companies to serve ads when
you use our website and apps:
Unity Ads
These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) when you use our website and apps in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used, please visit the relevant company websites. Alternatively you can opt out of third-party vendor's use of cookies for personalised advertising by visiting: aboutads.info
Cookies
We use cookies and other technologies to enable memberships and certain features
of membership (e.g. high score tracking, contest entries, etc). You may decline to provide personal
information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of
our features may not function properly as a result.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and
alteration of the information under our control.
Children's Guidelines
The Ezone website and apps do:
NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent
or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent
to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity. Without
prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond
directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes
without prior parental consent
NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information
NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information
NOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally
identifiable contact information
NOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity,
to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this
site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
Simon Edis
Ezone PTY LTD
Perth, Western Australia
